My goodness…
Take them away.
OLD WOUNDS ARE REOPENED
Brother.
Are you a police lady?
Yes.
I'm Jodie.
What's your name?
Liezel.
That's a pretty name.
Listen here, I don't think it's necessary…
I'm sorry about your grandfather.
-Why do you want to go there…
-Open the damn garage!
We have a warrant.
Get inside the house, quickly!
Come on, move it!
Quickly. Move, move! Come on!
Come on, come on. Hurry up!
Come on, come on.
My goodness, get in!
Thanks, Gert.
Get in.
That one has been used up.
Hey, guys, go to bed, you know the rules.
Hey, get out of the way!
-Are you all right? Where's your phone?
-What's going on?
-Where's Katlego and Naledi?
-In their room.
Pack some things.
Take them to your sister's.
-What's happening?
-I need you to trust me, Agnes, please.
Don't ask questions,
I can't answer them.
VOTE NATIONAL PARTY
Get the lights.
Start moving, come on.
What the fuck is going on?
He's been shot!
Secure the area!